(Leslie:)Boy, your heart's racing.
I must have really gotten you going.
(Howard:)Well, it's partly you.
(Howard:)Partly my transient, idiopathic arrhythmia.
(Leslie:)Sexy.
(Howard:)Can I assume that
you've likewise found the experience...?
(Leslie:)Satisfactory?
(Howard:)That wasn't quite the word
I was looking for...
(Howard:)...but sure, I'll do this pass-fail.
(Leslie:)Hey, are you enjoying
that prototyper I got you?
(Howard:)Oh, it's great. Everybody in the Engineering
Department is eating their hearts out.
(Leslie:)Isn't it nice when your good fortune
makes others miserable?
(Howard:)You know, most people don't get that.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, I'm home!
- Oh, great.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Book club was canceled.